FADHLIL AZHIM FIRMANSYAH

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

082324444770 | fadhlilazfi@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/fadhlilazfi/ | github.com/fadhlil18

Pandeglang, Indonesia

A bachelor degree of Computer Engineering from Telkom University. Experienced as a Front-End Developer with HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, and React. Currently studying in bootcamp program for deepening skills in Web Developer. A detail-oriented individual who is eager for a full-time opportunity in Front End Web Development.

Project Experience

Web Project- Dicoding Final Project

Aug, 2023 - Sep, 2023

Front-End Developer

- Developed a popular games website using HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Created a popular games responsive website for final project

Game Application - Collage Thesis Project

Jan, 2022 - Jul, 2022

Game Developer

- Developed Game App using Game Maker Studio
- Created UI and assets for this Game Project
- Developed AI using Intelligent Agent

Mobile Application – Collage Group Project

Feb, 2021 - Jun, 2021

Front-End Developer

- Developed Mobile App using React Native
- Developed project with Figma and Photoshop
- Developed Application using Maps and Camera API

Work Experiences

PT. Telekomunikasi Indonesia - Bandung, Indonesia

Jul, 2021 - Sep, 2021

Civil Mechanical and Electrical

- Made Maintenance Videos for Civil Mechanical Electrical devices examination
- Data collection of Civil Mechanical Electrical tools at each STO Witel of West Bandung
- Input STO Witel of West Bandung data to Web Application

PT. POS Indonesia- Pandeglang, Indonesia

Jul, 2020 - Sep, 2020

Service, Logistic, and Marketing

- Served customers who need delivery good services
- Checking incoming and outgoing goods
- Examined and data collection on the delivery of ID cards, tax letters and family letters.

Education Level

Telkom University - Bandung, Indonesia

2018 - 2022

Bachelor Degree of Computer Engineering, 3.44/4.00

- Thesis: Infected Person Behavior Design in Doctor Vs Virus Game Using Intelligent Agent
- Relevant Course Works: Database, Web Development, Mobile App Development, System, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Native, and Management Project.
- Certificate: https://drive.google.com/file/d/11LD68Wmy-II5LgSqu-KsUbdKJjlDihwA/view?usp=drive_link

Courses, Training and Certifications

Harisenin.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

Feb, 2024 - Jul, 2024

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp, -/4.00

- Final Project: Clone Airbnb Website
- Relevant Course works: Web Development, Management Project, Git, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, and ReactJS.
- On-Going Project: https://github.com/ahyarfatahillah/grub-4-FSD11-react/tree/develop

Dicoding.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

Aug, 2023 - Oct, 2023

Basic Programing Web and Javascript

• Final Project: Designed and developed a website popular games website, within one month

• Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

• Certificate: https://drive.google.com/file/d/14zPidtwVwa1CdWPHj1m12qxFlkeJ8g5W/view?usp=drive-link

Certificate: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1mCTO-pe8w2CaFIGI3QcyY8O5vda-i40w/view?usp=drive_link

Coursenet.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

Javascript and Node.js

Final Project: Count perfect vowels, within one day

• Relevant Course works: Javascript and Node.js

Certificate: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1rusH4TIYvcdxVOkBmRHOX_pq9vSza9Cz/view?usp=drive_link

Skills and Other Experience

Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Tailwind, ReactJS, Python, C, C++, Figma, and Github.

Soft skills: Positive Attitude, Self-Control, Flexibility, Problem Solving, Time Management, Analytical Thinking and Teamwork.

Languages: Indonesia (Native) and English (Intermediate).

Sep, 2023